Danny Kaye and Sylvia Fine Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music, 1939-1985 (Box 1-427, 536-537, 641-765, 791)
  - The Danny Kaye Show, 1963-1967 (Box 1-282, 695-766)
    - Episode #16, 1963, December 18, 95504337
      - Verdict blues (Box-folder 38/5, 709/2)
      - Xmas season (Box-folder 39/1-2, 709/3)
      - You meet the nicest people (Box-folder 39/3, 709/4)
    - Episode #17, 1963, December 25, 95504339
      - Baby it's cold outside (Box-folder 40/1, 709/5)
      - Comes once in a lifetime (Box-folder 40/2, 709/6)
      - Dancing in the dark (Box-folder 40/3)
      - Dancing styles (Box-folder 40/4-5, 762)
      - In Vienna (Box-folder 41/1, 709/7)
      - Jingle journey, Versions with Peggy Lee, Jo Stafford, and Nat King Cole. (Box-folder 41/2-4, 709/8)
      - Jingle jungle, Alternative title: Jingle journey, version with Nat King Cole. (Box-folder 42/1)
      - Let there be peace on earth, Lyric sheet only (Box-folder 42/2)
      - Let's have another cup of coffee (Box-folder 42/3)
      - Love with a capitol "you" (Box-folder 42/4)
      - Old King Cole (Box-folder 42/5, 710/1)
      - That's how I feel (Box-folder 42/6, 710/2)
      - Vienna & reprise (Box-folder 42/7, 710/3-4)
    - Episode #18, 1964, January 8, 95504343
      - Big Louie (Box-folder 43/1, 710/5)
      - Bitter tea (Box-folder 43/2)
      - Check for two, Alternative title: Beguine (Box-folder 43/3)
      - Gangster hideout (Box-folder 43/4)
      - I'm five (Box-folder 43/5, 710/6)
      - John Henry (Box-folder 43/6, 710/7)
      - Lazy river (Box-folder 44/1, 710/8)
      - My love is a wanderer (Box-folder 44/2, 710/9)
      - New baby & Coda (Box-folder 44/3, 710/10)
      - Oak-aroma (Box-folder 44/4)
      - Prison camp (Box-folder 44/5, 710/11)
      - Ship waiter (Box-folder 44/6, 710/12)
      - Tea Coda (Box-folder 44/7, 710/13)
      - Tea for two (Box-folder 44/8, 710/14)
      - Tea is land (Box-folder 45/1, 711/1)
      - Tico tico (Box-folder 45/2, 711/2)
      - Vienna, Alternative title: Tea from Vienna Woods (Box-folder 45/3)
      - We belong together (Box-folder 45/4, 711/3)
    - Episode #19, 1964, January 15, 95504361; 95504365
      - Ain't it great to be crazy (Box-folder 46/1, 711/4)
      - Duck blind (Box-folder 46/2, 711/5)
      - Hit parade medley
        - Hit parade (Box-folder 46/3, 711/6)
        - 1. Close as pages in a book (Box-folder 46/4, 711/7)
        - 2. High on a windy hill (Box-folder 46/5, 711/8)
        - 3. Hold me (Box-folder 46/6, 711/9)
        - 4. It only happens when I dance with you (Box-folder 46/7, 711/10)
        - 5. Three little words (Box-folder 46/8, 711/11)
        - 6. The boy next door (Box-folder 46/9, 711/12)
        - 7. Something's coming (Box-folder 47/1, 711/13)
        - 8. When a gypsy makes his violin cry (Box-folder 47/2, 711/14)
        - 9. Hands across the table (Box-folder 47/3, 711/15)
        - 10. Johnny one-note (Box-folder 47/4, 711/16)
      - I wish you love (Box-folder 47/5, 711/17)
      - I won't dance (Box-folder 47/6, 711/18)
      - Magnum studios (Box-folder 48/1)
      - Marriage counselor (Box-folder 48/2, 712/1)
      - My walking cane, Other title: Hand me down my walkin' cane (Box-folder 48/3-4, 712/2)
      - Noel entry (Box-folder 48/5, 712/3)
    - Episode #20, 1964, January 22, 95504373
      - Birthday surprise (Box-folder 49/1, 712/4)
      - Blues dance (1 & 2) (Box-folder 49/2-5, 712/5)
      - Blues dance impressions (Box-folder 712/6)
      - Do you ever think of me (Box-folder 49/6)
      - Green grass (Box-folder 49/7)
      - Grand lummox march (Box-folder 50/1, 712/7)
      - Horror house (Box-folder 50/2, 712/8)
      - I like the likes of you (Box-folder 50/3, 712/9)
      - Ox drivers song & Coda (Box-folder 50/4, 712/10)
      - Pine concerto (Box-folder 50/5, 712/11)
      - Safety zone (Box-folder 50/6, 712/12)
    - Episode #21, 1964, January 29, 95504377
      - Barrel of beauty (Box-folder 51/1)
      - Chapanecas (Box-folder 51/2, 713/1)
      - Diahann Carroll (Box-folder 51/3-4, 713/2)
      - Father and the nurse (Box-folder 51/5, 713/3)
      - Fight game (Box-folder 51/6, 713/4)
      - Here comes the bride (Box-folder 52/1,713/5)
      - Jazz dance closing (Box-folder 52/2, 713/6)
      - Johnny one note (intro) (Box-folder 52/3)
      - "Nonsense songs" medley (Box-folder 52/4)
      - Put on a happy face (Box-folder 52/5, 713/7)
      - Spanish hat theme (Box-folder 52/6, 713/8)
      - Table dance (Box-folder 53/1-2, 713/9)
      - Three o'clock in the morn (Box-folder 53/3, 713/10)
      - Viva papata (Box-folder 53/4, 713/11)
      - Wedding march (Box-folder 53/5, 713/12)
      - Welcome to yama song, Lyric sheet only. (Box-folder 53/6)
      - When the saints go marching in, Lyric sheet only. (Box-folder 53/7)
    - Episode #22, 1964, February 5, 95504540
      - Action station (Box-folder 54/1, 713/13)
      - Can can impressions (Box-folder 54/2-3, 713/14)
      - Competition time (Box-folder 54/4, 714/1)
      - Crazy Barbara & Coda (Box-folder 54/5, 714/2)
      - He's a mountie (Box-folder 55/1, 714/3)
      - He's a mountie (closing) (Box-folder 55/2, 714/4)
      - I miss my Swiss (Box-folder 55/3)
      - In-Saskatchewan (Box-folder 55/4)
      - Marching along together (Box-folder 55/5, 714/5)
      - Mountie B.G. (Box-folder 55/6, 714/6)
      - Mr. Hummingbird, Alternative title: Mr. Hummingbird, hello (Box-folder 55/7, 714/7)
      - San Francisco bay blues (Box-folder 55/8, 714/8)
      - Saskatchewan (Box-folder 56/1, 714/9)
      - Shall we dance (Box-folder 56/2-3, 714/10)
      - Swiss ambassador (1-3) (Box-folder 56/4, 57/1-2, 714/11-13)
    - Episode #23, 1964, February 19, 95504782
      - Beethoven minuet (Box-folder 57/3, 715/1)
      - English judge (Box-folder 57/4, 715/2)
      - Farewell my Cindy Jane (Box-folder 57/5, 715/3)
      - H.M.S. Cruelty (Box-folder 57/6, 715/4)
      - Just in time (Box-folder 57/7, 715/5)
      - Minuet in "G" (Box-folder 57/8, 715/6)
      - A shine on your shoes (Box-folder 715/7)
      - Teen-ager (Box-folder 58/1, 715/8)
      - Thru the customs (Box-folder 58/2, 715/9)
      - When I take my sugar to tea (Box-folder 58/3, 715/10)
      - With a shine on your shoes (Box-folder 58/4-5)
    - Episode #24, 1964, February 26, 95504862
      - Finale - hillbilly sketch (Box-folder 59/1, 715/11)
      - Hey look me over (Box-folder 59/2, 715/12)
      - I caught a bear (Box-folder 59/3, 715/13)
      - I didn't catch an owl (Box-folder 59/4, 715/14)
      - Intro to Buddy Ebsen (Box-folder 59/5)
      - Let's take a walk, Other titles: Let's take a walk around the block; Let's walk around the block (Box-folder 60/1-2)
      - Marching along, Other title: Marching along together (Box-folder 60/3)
      - Mountain stew (Box-folder 60/4)
      - Pappy clunk (Box-folder 60/5, 715/15)
      - Secret service (Box-folder 61/1, 715/16)
      - Soon it's gonna rain (Box-folder 61/2)
      - Uninvited guest (Box-folder 61/3, 715/17)
      - Wonderful guy (Box-folder 61/4-5, 715/18)
    - Episode #25, 1964, March 4, 95505229
      - Big Mike (Box-folder 62/1, 716/1)
      - Butler and maid (Box-folder 62/2, 716/2)
      - Down by the winegar woiks (Box-folder 62/3, 716/3)
      - Flamenco capers (Box-folder 62/4, 716/4)
      - Lawrence of Alcatrez (Box-folder 62/5)
      - More I cannot wish for you, Lyric sheet only. (Box-folder 63/1)
      - Music box (Box-folder 63/2, 716/5)
      - Now is the hour (Box-folder 63/3, 716/6)
      - Proposal time (Box-folder 63/4, 716/7)
      - Sevilla (Box-folder 63/5)
      - They all laughed (Box-folder 63/6, 716/8)
      - Winegar woiks (Box-folder 63/4, 64/1, 716/9)
    - Episode #26, 1964, March 25, 95505041
      - Bunch o' blues (Box-folder 64/2)
      - Carnival of Venice (Box-folder 717/1)
      - Carnival of Venice (jazz) (Box-folder 717/2)
      - Dr. Yes (Box-folder 64/3, 717/3)
      - Fourth man theme (Box-folder 64/4, 717/4)
      - I love a piano (Box-folder 64/5, 717/5)
      - King Tut (Box-folder 64/6, 717/6)
      - Mama Luigi's (Box-folder 65/1)
      - The music stopped (Box-folder 65/2-4, 717/7)
      - Yankee Doodle (Box-folder 65/5, 717/8)
    - Episode #27, 1964, March 18, 95505143
      - Desert camel blues (Box-folder 65/6, 717/9)
      - Desert closing (Box-folder 65/7, 717/10)
      - Desert men (Box-folder 66/1, 717/11)
      - Heart of my heart (Box-folder 66/2, 717/12)
      - Old fashioned (Box-folder 66/3, 717/13)
      - Surfside baby, Other title: Surftide baby (Box-folder 66/4, 67/1, 717/14)
      - Time to hit (Box-folder 67/2, 717/15)
      - You're under arrest, Other titles: The moment I saw ya; My heart's on the brink (Box-folder 67/3, 717/16)
    - Episode #28, 1964, April 1, 95505230
      - Alone together (Box-folder 67/4, 718/1)
      - Blast off (Box-folder 68/1, 718/2)
      - Change partners (Box-folder 68/2-3, 718/3)
      - Consider yourself (Box-folder 68/4, 718/4)
      - Cup of coffee, Other titles: Let's have another cup of coffee (Box-folder 69/1, 718/5)
      - Friendship club (Box-folder 69/2, 718/6)
      - Hit parade, Caption title: H. P. #. (Box-folder 69/3)
        - 1. Some enchanted evening (Box-folder 69/4)
        - 2. I won't dance (Box-folder 69/5)
        - 3. I talk to the trees (Box-folder 69/6, 718/7)
        - 4. Smoke gets in your eyes (Box-folder 69/7, 718/8)
        - 5. Beer barrel polka (Box-folder 69/8, 718/9)
        - 6. Dancing in the dark (Box-folder 69/9, 718/10)
        - 7. Let's have another piece of pie (Box-folder 70/1, 718/11)
        - 8. Dancing on the ceiling (Box-folder 70/2, 718/12)
        - 9. Near you (Box-folder 70/3, 718/13)
        - 10. Another piece of pie (Box-folder 70/4, 718/14)
        - 11. You do something to me (Box-folder 70/5, 718/15)
        - 12. Got a date with an angel (Box-folder 70/6, 718/16)
        - 13. Something to remember you by (Box-folder 70/7, 718/17)
        - 14. Piece of pie (Box-folder 70/8, 718/18)
      - It's that time of the year (Box-folder 71/1-2, 718/19)
      - Manhattan (Box-folder 71/3, 718/20)
      - Tequila mockingbird (Box-folder 71/4)
      - Vienna woods (Box-folder 71/5, 718/21)
      - Where or when (Box-folder 71/6, 718/22)
    - Episode #29, 1964, April 8, 95505406; 95505454
      - Gigi (Box-folder 72/1)
      - I ain't down yet (Box-folder 72/2-4, 719/1)
      - Long hot supper (Box-folder 72/5, 719/2)
      - Look out for Mamma (Box-folder 72/6, 719/3)
      - Western impressions (Box-folder 73/1-2, 719/4)
      - Whistle while you work (Box-folder 73/3-4, 719/5)
    - Episode #30, 1964, April 15, 95505559
      - Irish mother (Box-folder 74/1, 719/6)
      - It's that time of year (Box-folder 74/2)
      - Marriage pronunciation (Box-folder 74/3, 719/7)
      - Roberta and the maid (Box-folder 74/4, 719/8)
      - Steppin' out with my baby (Box-folder 74/5, 577, 764)
      - 30's production (1-4), Other title: Part 1: Everything I have is yours (Box-folder 74/6, 75/1-3, 719/10)
    - Episode #31, 1964, April 22, 95505681
      - Around the world (Box-folder 76/1, 720/1)
      - Art gallery (Box-folder 76/2, 720/2)
      - Ballin' the jack (Box-folder 76/3, 720/3)
      - My lady loves to dance, Other title: My ladies love to dance (Box-folder 76/4-5, 720/4)
      - Suite for odd-ball instruments (Box-folder 77/1, 720/5)
      - Tall hope (Box-folder 77/2, 720/6)
      - This way please (Box-folder 77/3, 720/7)
    - Episode #32, 1964, April 29, 95505758; 95506185
      - Barber chair switch (Box-folder 77/4, 720/8)
      - Danny boy Italian (Box-folder 77/5, 720/9)
      - Donna Reed theme (Box-folder 77/6, 720/10)
      - Farewell Cindy Jane (Box-folder 77/7)
      - I'll remember April (Box-folder 77/8)
      - In Vienna (Box-folder 77/9)
      - Late spot (Box-folder 77/10, 720/11)
      - Mention my name in Sheboygan (Box-folder 78/1-2, 720/12)
      - Mountain greenery (Box-folder 78/3, 720/13)
      - Nursies (Box-folder 78/4, 720/14)
      - Petticoat junction (Box-folder 78/5, 720/15)
    - Episode #33, 1964, November 25, 95506002
      - Argument anatomy (Box-folder 79/1)
      - Big elopement (Box-folder 79/2-3)
      - Cope with the pony (1-3) (Box-folder 80/1-4)
      - The fair in a day (Box-folder 81/1-2)
      - Here's Danny (Box-folder 81/3)
      - I've got your number (Box-folder 82/1-3)
      - Just in time (Box-folder 82/4, 721/1)
      - On stage (Box-folder 83/1)
      - Roll call (Box-folder 83/2)
      - Sweat shirt (Box-folder 83/3)
      - Water boy (Box-folder 83/4)
    - Episode #34, 1964, October 21, 95506008
      - A buddy by the name of "you" (Box-folder 83/5-6)
      - Late snack (Box-folder 84/1)
      - Lulu's back in town (Box-folder 84/2)
      - Night with the piranhas (Box-folder 84/3)
      - On the street (Box-folder 84/4)
      - South Rampart Street parade (Box-folder 84/5)
    - Episode #35, 1964, September 23, 95506488
      - Blind date (Box-folder 84/6)
      - Do you ever think of me (Box-folder 84/7, 721/2)
      - Foggy day (Box-folder 84/8)
      - Huckleberry duck (Box-folder 85/1-2)
      - What is love (Box-folder 85/3-4)
    - Episode #36, 1964, February 10, 95506557
      - Broadway wedding (Box-folder 86/1)
      - Deadwood stage (Box-folder 86/2)
      - Green socks (Box-folder 86/3)
      - Little dutch treat (Box-folder 86/4)
      - The millionaire's lament (Box-folder 87/1)
      - On to New Haven (Box-folder 87/2)
      - Running wild (Box-folder 87/3-4)
      - Sad Bernie (Box-folder 87/5)
      - The show's a hit (Box-folder 88/1)
      - The tapioca (Box-folder 88/2-3)
      - They call the wind Maria (Box-folder 88/4)
    - Episode #37, 1964, December 30, 95506611; 95507058; 95507063
      - Ain't she sweet (Box-folder 88/5)
      - Bidin' my time (Box-folder 89/1)
      - Bidin' my time (coda) (Box-folder 89/2)
      - Checkstand four (Box-folder 89/3)
      - Cindy Sue (Box-folder 89/4)
      - Mountain feud (Box-folder 89/5)
      - Sentimental journey (Box-folder 90/1-3)
      - T.V. waltz revels (Box-folder 91/1-2)
    - Episode #38, 1964, October 28, 95507692
      - The ballad of Little Red Ridin' Hood (Box-folder 91/3-4, 92/1-4)
      - Control yourself (Box-folder 93/1, 721/3)
      - English courtroom (Box-folder 93/2)
      - I get along without you (Box-folder 93/3)
      - Look who's dancing (Box-folder 93/4-5)
      - Paper clip job (Box-folder 93/6)
    - Episode #39, 1964, September 30, 95507895
      - Ain't nobody here but us chickens (Box-folder 94/1)
      - Arabian magic (Box-folder 94/2)
      - Candy butcher playoff (Box-folder 94/3)
      - Don't put a tax, Other title: Don't put a tax on a beautiful girl (Box-folder 94/4)
      - Jamboree Jones (Box-folder 94/5)
      - Japanese sunset (Box-folder 95/1, 721/4)
      - Lady of Spain (Box-folder 95/2)
      - Late night party (Box-folder 95/3)
      - You make me feel so young (Box-folder 95/4)
      - You're my everything (Box-folder 95/5)
    - Episode #40, 1964, October 7, 95508025
      - The first day (Box-folder 95/6)
      - The gift (Box-folder 96/1)
      - Gypsy (2,4,8,9) (Box-folder 96/2-5)
      - Gypsy camp (Box-folder 96/6, 721/5)
      - Gypsy cries (Box-folder 96/7)
      - Gypsy life (Box-folder 96/8)
      - Gypsy wedding (Box-folder 96/9)
      - Happy birthday to the birthday girl (Box-folder 96/10)
      - Hey gypsy (Box-folder 96/11)
      - Marching adorables, Other title: Marching along together (Box-folder 97/1-2)
      - No strings (Box-folder 97/3-4)
      - They'll never break us, Other titles: You'll never break us; They'll never break the two of us in half; Since I met my Yasha (Box-folder 97/5)
      - Where is the man (Box-folder 97/6)
    - Episode #41, 1964, October 14, 95508243
      - British murder (Box-folder 98/1)
      - Fat on a hot tin roof (Box-folder 98/2)
      - I've got a loverly bunch of cocoanuts (Box-folder 98/3-4)
      - Jonathon Edwards playoff (Box-folder 98/5)
      - Let's watch television (Box-folder 98/6)
      - Piano roll blues (Box-folder 99/1)
      - Spelling song, Other title: Mary Tyler Moore (Box-folder 99/2)
      - Ten cents a dance (1 & 2) (Box-folder 99/3-5)
    - Episode #42, 1964, November 4, 95508332; 95508359
      - Balloon dance (Box-folder 100/1-2)
      - Fire the maid (Box-folder 100/3)
      - Here I'll stay (Box-folder 100/4, 721/6)
      - Medley (Pennies - Nevertheless) (Box-folder 101/1)
      - Slap that bass (Box-folder 101/2)
      - Way back home (Box-folder 101/3)
    - Episode #43, 1965, March 17, 95508405
      - The amateur doctor (Box-folder 101/4)
      - Anvil playoff (Box-folder 101/5)
      - Do-re-mi (Box-folder 101/6)
      - Heart alone (Box-folder 101/7)
      - Irish tag (Box-folder 102/1)
      - The Irish traveller (Box-folder 102/2)
      - Laura (Box-folder 102/3-4)
      - Little man (Box-folder 102/5)
      - Sweet Molly Malone (Box-folder 102/6)
      - Skylark, Other title: Listen to the song of the skylark (Box-folder 102/7)
      - Stairway to paradise (Box-folder 102/8)
    - Episode #44, 1964, November 11, 95508565
      - Cherry pie (Box-folder 103/1)
      - Italian street singer (Box-folder 103/2)
      - Organ grinders song (Box-folder 103/3)
      - The questions children ask (Box-folder 103/4)
      - Rehearsal hall revue, Other title: Rehearsal hall mix-up (Box-folder 103/5, 104/1)
      - Turkey with stuffing (Box-folder 104/2)
      - When the saints go marching in (Box-folder 104/3)
      - You are my sunshine (Box-folder 104/4)
    - Episode #45, 1964, November 18, 95508803
      - Baroque princess (Box-folder 104/5)
      - Circus impressions (Box-folder 105/1)
      - Flight (Box-folder 105/2)
      - Personality (Box-folder 105/3)
      - Pick yourself up (Box-folder 105/4)
      - The questions children ask (Box-folder 105/5)
      - This is the army (Box-folder 106/1)
      - Up above my head (Box-folder 106/2)
    - Episode #46, 1964, December 2, 95508805
      - Act I & act II (Box-folder 106/3)
      - Act II & act III (Box-folder 106/4)
      - The best things, Other title: The best things in life are cheap (Box-folder 106/5)
      - Broadway (Box-folder 107/1, 721/7)
      - Don Chernando's song (Box-folder 107/2)
      - Drive to work (Box-folder 107/3)
      - I just waxed my heart (Box-folder 107/4)
      - If this isn't love (Box-folder 107/5-6)
      - Iowa (Box-folder 108/1)
      - Irish melody (Box-folder 108/2)
      - Mother Goose (Box-folder 108/3-5)
      - Murder, maestro, please (Box-folder 109/1)
      - No good (Box-folder 109/2)
      - Our two hearts (Box-folder 109/3)
      - Public lover #1 (Box-folder 109/4)
      - Shtubbleveiss (Box-folder 109/5)
      - That stinks (Box-folder 109/6)
      - The trouble song (Box-folder 109/7)
      - The trouble song (finale) (Box-folder 109/8)
      - Underneath a shiny moon (Box-folder 109/9)
      - We're the sailor boys (Box-folder 109/10)
      - Who wants to be a millionaire (Box-folder 109/11)
    - Episode #47, 1964, December 9, 95508806
      - Cute & Cute dance (Box-folder 110/1)
      - Japanese teenager (Box-folder 110/2)
      - Old MacDonald (Box-folder 110/3)
      - Our two hearts (Box-folder 110/4)
      - Santa Claus Rudy (Box-folder 111/1)
      - Space capsule (Box-folder 111/2)
      - Swan lake (Box-folder 111/3-4)
      - We're the sailor boys (Box-folder 112/1-2)
    - Episode #48, 1964, December 16, 95508981
      - Changing of the guard (Box-folder 112/3)
      - Didn't it rain (Box-folder 112/4)
      - Frere Jacques (Box-folder 112/5)
      - Heavenly music (Box-folder 113/1)
      - Jerome comes to dinner (Box-folder 113/2)
      - La vie en rose (Box-folder 113/3)
      - Luncheon with history (Box-folder 113/4)
      - Oh promise me (Box-folder 113/5, 721/8)
      - Story of Alice (Box-folder 113/6)
    - Episode #49, 1964, December 23, 95508998
      - Christmas fantasy, Other title: Christmas interlude (Box-folder 113/7, 114/1)
      - Fanfares (Box-folder 114/2)
      - Jingle journey (Box-folder 114/3)
      - He's gone away (Box-folder 114/4)
      - Old friends (Box-folder 114/5)
      - Santa Claus (Box-folder 114/6)
      - Santa Claus is comin' to town (Box-folder 114/7)
      - Sleep well little children (Box-folder 114/8)
      - The spy (Box-folder 115/1)
      - Villie villie (Box-folder 115/2)
      - Waltz around the Xmas tree, Other title: Waltz 'round the Xmas tree (Box-folder 115/3-4)
      - Xmas waltz (intro) (Box-folder 115/5)
    - Episode #50, 1965, January 6, 95508999
      - Ajax theme (Box-folder 116/1)
      - El ringo (Box-folder 116/2)
      - Here we are in school again (Box-folder 116/3)
      - Hit parade medley
        - 1. Them there eyes (Box-folder 116/4)
        - 2. I'm gonna wash that man (Box-folder 116/5)
        - 3. Willow weep for me (Box-folder 116/6)
        - 4. A lot of livin' to do (Box-folder 116/7)
        - 5. Embraceable you (Box-folder 116/8)
        - 6. Let's call the whole thing off (Box-folder 116/9)
        - 7. Another openin'- another show (Box-folder 116/10)
        - 8. Why was I born (Box-folder 116/11)
        - 9. It's a grand night for singing (Box-folder 116/12)
        - 10. There will never be another you (Box-folder 117/1)
        - 11. My heart stood still (Box-folder 117/2)
        - 12. Manhattan (Box-folder 117/3)
        - 13. The party's over (Box-folder 117/4)
        - 14. Pistol packin' mama (Box-folder 117/5)
      - I'm beginning to see the light (Box-folder 117/6)
      - Mother Goose on the loose (Box-folder 117/7)
      - Pretty baby (Box-folder 117/8)
      - School days (Box-folder 118/1)
      - Tacos please (Box-folder 118/2)
      - What is this thing (Box-folder 118/3)
    - Episode #51, 1965, January 13, 95509142
      - Big time scientist (Box-folder 118/4)
      - Come rain or come shine (Box-folder 118/5)
      - I like flying (D flat), Versions in D flat and E flat. (Box-folder 118/6, 119/1)
      - Jerome at the dentist (Box-folder 119/2)
      - Too long at the fair (Box-folder 119/3)
      - Triplets (Box-folder 119/4)
      - Variations in rhythm (Box-folder 120/1-2)
    - Episode #52, 1965, January 20, 95509303
      - Acrobats opening (Box-folder 121/1)
      - Circus II (Box-folder 121/2)
      - Do-re-mi (Box-folder 121/3)
      - He has to help himself (Box-folder 121/4)
      - Hitchcock movie (Box-folder 121/5)
      - How to laugh (Box-folder 121/6, 721/9)
      - Italian movie (Box-folder 122/1)
      - Life is just a bunch of cherries, Other title: Life is just a bowl of cherries (Box-folder 122/2)
      - The new wig (Box-folder 122/3)
      - Play a simple melody (Box-folder 122/4)
      - Russian Cinderella (Box-folder 123/1)
      - Say your magic word (Box-folder 123/2)
      - Seymour and the gladiators (Box-folder 123/3)
      - Walt Disney movie (Box-folder 123/4)
    - Episode #53, 1965, January 27, 95509315
      - Big bad wolf (Box-folder 123/5)
      - Bigger and better (Box-folder 124/1-2)
      - Carry me back (Box-folder 124/3)
      - Hooray for Hollywood. (Box-folder 124/4)
      - The menace (Box-folder 124/5)
      - Mother (Box-folder 125/1)
      - Mother opera (Box-folder 125/2)
      - Outer space (Box-folder 125/3)
      - Rock around the clock (Box-folder 125/4)
      - A shot in the mouth (Box-folder 125/5)
      - Spellbound (Box-folder 125/6)
      - We belong together (Box-folder 126/1)
      - Wild one (Box-folder 126/2)
      - Wonderful world (Box-folder 126/3)
    - Episode #54, 1965, February 3, 95509334
      - Cakewalk dance (Box-folder 126/4-5)
      - Cakewalk dance (finale) (Box-folder 127/1-2)
      - Cool water (Box-folder 127/3)
      - Drama class (Box-folder 127/4)
      - Glocca morro (intro) (Box-folder 127/5)
      - Night court (Box-folder 127/6)
      - Putting all my eggs in one basket (Box-folder 127/7)
      - Waltzing Matilda (Box-folder 128/1)